[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these US states have an official motto related to liberty. Spot the odd one.", "correct_answer": "Oklahoma", "incorrect_answers": ["Iowa", "New Jersey", "New Hampshire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The timeline in the story takes place between which 2 significant Holidays? (roughly)", "correct_answer": "Between Christmas and New Years", "incorrect_answers": ["Between Easter Sunday and Memorial Day", "Between the 4th of July and Labor day", "Between Secretarys Day and Bosses Day"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first singer to get a Gold Record for a single?", "correct_answer": "Perry Como", "incorrect_answers": ["Tex Beneke", "Elvis Presley", "Frank Sinatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the value of the smallest valued coin ever issued by the US Treasury?", "correct_answer": "one half of a cent", "incorrect_answers": ["one cent", "one eighth of a cent", "one quarter of a cent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1966 was found the first ant fossil. From which geological period did it come from?", "correct_answer": "Cretaceous", "incorrect_answers": ["Pennsylvannian", "Pre-Fermaceous", "Jurasic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The original version of Cape Fear was released in 1962.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Midnight Run, Jack used to be a detective. What police department did he work in?", "correct_answer": "Chicago Police Department", "incorrect_answers": ["The Philadelphia Police Department", "New York City Police Department", "Los Angeles Police Department"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Greek mythology, Zeus saved one of Asclepius students from his wrath by turning him into this flower.", "correct_answer": "Peony", "incorrect_answers": ["Rose", "Forget-me-not", "Dahlia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Salt water crocodiles belong to the amphibian group.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the southern part of the United States, what months are peak season for tornadoes?", "correct_answer": "March-May", "incorrect_answers": ["June-August", "January-Feburary", "September-December"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about Tasmanian devils?", "correct_answer": "They are predominantly solitary animals", "incorrect_answers": ["They live in couples", "They live in groups", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where do Cheech and Chong sell marijuana in their third movie Nice Dreams?", "correct_answer": "From an ice cream truck", "incorrect_answers": ["In a fitness gym", "In an auto detail shop", "None of these"]}]